So now that we have seen how to update the firmware in Proxmox three, in this video, we are going
to see some basic commands and see if we can find key A or key B using some vulnerability tests in Proxmox
three.
So let's just start the Proxmox three tool and make sure your Proxmox three device is connected.
So we'll run proc spark three and Indiv t acm zero.
So right now it's giving error.
Let's just exit out.
And make sure our rocks three is device connected correctly.
So let's just disconnect one time and let's just reconnect it.
And we will run the same command again.
And now it's connected.
So first we will check the Uuid of this card.
Or let's just first run help command to check all the options.
So these are all the options.
So we can plot data, we can check high frequency card, we can check the hardware using command.
Then there is Lf for low frequency and then there are other commands for other type of cards.
Right?
So our focus is on high frequency cards because mifare cards are high frequency cards.
So let's just run SRF first.
And when you learn, you will see all the other options available in Cart, right?
So we have to read the ID of this cart.
So these cards are ISO one, 4443, a RFID cards, ISO certified cards.
So what we have to do is we have to type.
Then we have to type 14 A, You can see the command over here and then we have to type read.
So it will display the Uid of this card.
Similarly, we can change the card and see the Uid of another card.
Okay, so I've placed another card, and let's just run this command again.
So as you can see, the Uid is different.
Now it's E2DE0519 and the above card is E2391B19.
Right.
So this is how you can check the Uuid of any card.
Let me place the previous card again and let's just do.
One more time.
And these are Mifare cards, right?
So there's another command for Mifare.
So what you have to do is you have to type Xf and then space MF to see all the options in Mifare card.
Let's just hit enter and you can see all the other options which are available in VFR card, right?
So you can do help and you can set the card in debug mode.
Then you can read the block, read the sector, dump the card, you can restore Mifare classic binary
file, write the block, and then there is check option to check all the block keys.
And then there are other options for magic card as well.
We will see different options as well in our coming videos.
Right?
So let's just first check out the all the keys in this card.
So we will do.
H.f..
MF and.
Chk to check all the keys in the card over here you can see test all block keys.
So let's just type SSC.
And then you will see options related to this command.
Check command.
Right.
So we we don't know any key right now.
So we will just run.
And then there is option.
There are multiple options over here.
We will go these option one by one.
So first option, which we have to give is, uh, whether we are going to check a single sector or all
the sectors.
So we will check all the sectors.
So for all the sectors we just have to type star and then we have to type the card type.
Basically, this is one card you can check two card and four card as well.
So for one card you just have to type one because these are one cards right?
Then over here, if you know any key, basically if you know key A or key B from any sector, you can
just type A or B if you know the B key and then you can type the key B or key, whichever key, you
know.
But right now, we don't know any key anything about this card or we don't know any keys installed in
this card.
So we will just do question mark.
So till now, the command is very simple.
First, you have to type H for high frequency, then Mifare card.
Then we are checking the card.
So there is a command.
Then we will type.
Then we have type star so that we can check all the sectors.
Then this is the one card.
So we have just type one and then we don't know any key.
So we have just type question mark.
Then there are different options t, d, s and dz.
So basically these are different algorithm s is for slow timeout and s is for very slow time execution,
right?
So what we will do is we will just try to get the keys in our emulator memory so that we get the keys
directly into our Mac and device, right.
So for that we have to type T small t option so it will check all the keys and try to find all the keys.
Right.
And let's just hit enter.
So over here you can see all the manufacturer keys are found easily.
But over here in Sector five, the sector which we modified, right.
And the sector which we update.
And we also changed the keys of this sector.
So it's unknown over here, you can see we are not able to find the keys for Sector five.
All the other manufacturer keys are easily identifiable.
So these keys are found, but sector five keys are not found.
So there is a question mark over here, so we will see how we can find the keys of Sector five.
So let's just run one more time.
Now we'll run a nested test attack.
Basically, it's a nested authentication attack.
So what we have to do is we have to type nested over here.
There's a nested command.
So we will do F and F and nested.
So right now it's giving us all the options.
So basically there are simple commands available.
So if, you know, let's just go through these options again.
So the first option over here is the card memory.
And the card memory is one, as I told you, because we are using one card, so we will do F.
MF nested.
And these are one key cards, right?
So we have to type one.
Then over here we can give the block number as well.
But still, we don't know any block or any data from any block.
So we have to type star, right?
Then again, we will transfer all the data in our emulator memory.
So we will type T So let me go through this command one more time for high frequency for method card.
And then we are running nested attack on one card.
So we have type one.
And if we know any block or any key in any block, we have to type the block number and then we can
give the key so it will retrieve all the other keys from all the other sectors.
Right?
But currently we don't know any sector or any block keys, so we will just type.
Star and then t t for transferring all the keys into our emulator memory.
Right.
So let's just hit enter.
And you can see it has found key for sector five in just seconds.
So how it's possible.
How how this thing is possible.
This thing is possible because we haven't updated all the manufacturer keys.
So keeping all the manufacturer keys in a default manner.
The actual sector which we modified is easily findable.
So you have to one thing, you have to make sure whenever you modify any sector, you have to modify
the keys for all the sectors, no matter which sector you have modified.
So let me go through this one more time.
So in this case, I have just modified the things in sector five and then I just updated the key A and
key B of Sector five, and I have kept all the keys and all the other data from all the other sectors
in a in a transport configuration, which was the, which was the configuration in which we have received
this card.
So what you have to do is whenever you modify any sector, you have to modify the keys of that sector
as well as you have to modify all the other sector keys.
So no matter if you use that sector or not, you have to modify all the sectors.
So we have found the key.
Now let's just try to read data for Sector five.
So let's just do one more time.
And to read sector.
There is a simple command to read the sector.
That is SC to read the sector.
So let's just type h f f.
RDC.
And then we have to give the key and the block or the sector number, sorry.
So we have to give the sector five and we will pass key A and let's just copy key A from here.
And let's just paste it.
So F is for reading the sector and we have to read sector five.
So let's just hit enter.
Let's just run it one more time.
It happens.
Sorry.
We have to give the space in the key type and the key number over here.
So I will just not passing the space.
That's why this error was coming.
So let's just do it one more time.
So over here you can see we have easily read the Complete Sector.
So the first two blocks are empty, but the third block you can see is a value block.
So you can see it from its configuration, the first four bytes, then the next four bytes, then again,
the four bytes are repeated.
Then again, there is a complement.
So this is how you read sector using key A in Proxmox three.
So it's quite easy.
You can also modify the sector or you can also modify the blocks.
There is another command to write the blocks you can see this is the command, so let's just copy it.
And we have to do again.
Then we have to type this command.
And then we can see how to write data in any block using this sample.
Right?
So we can type the block number.
Then we have to type the key and then we can type the data in hexadecimal format.
So this is how you write data in Proc three So in the next video we are going to see what if we have
modified all the keys in all the sectors and we have just kept one key unmodified?
Are we still able to do the same attack again?
We will see this in our next video, so we will see if we have modified all the keys.
And we have just kept one key remain remaining in the manufacture format.
Still, we are able to do the same attack or not.